One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
We're approaching the exit.
出口が近いね
Going straight down, full steam ahead!
このまま一気に下るよ
No way!
えっ　ウソ…
What?!
えっ…
Wh-Whaaaat?!
ええっ　ええーっ…
Alright, the sea train has emerged!
よーし！海列車が出てきたあ！
Let's go, guys! We're fighting, too!
野郎ども！こっちも出撃だ！
– Yeah!
–　おう！
Jump, Sodom and Gomorrah!
跳べ！ソドム！ゴモラ！
Wh-What the...?!
な…　何だ？
Mr. Straw Hat!
麦わらさーん！
On behalf of the entire Franky Family,
フランキー一家全員まとめて
thank you for taking us along!
お世話になりまーす！
Fire the connection cannons!
連結砲！撃てーっ！
Whoa! Cool!
うっほー！すっげえ！
Those are some top-of-the-line king bulls.
ありゃ最上ランクのキングブルらねえ
Not bad!
やるなあ！
Dammit! Those bastards...!
ちくしょう…　あの野郎ども！
Hey dumbasses, watch it!
てめえら！ムチャすな！
– Thanks for your help!
–　よろしく！
Looks like the tracks have drifted quite a bit.
だいぶ流されてるね
But I've watched over the sea train from day one.
だが 開発から海列車を見てきたあたしを
Don't underestimate me!
なめんじゃらいよ
I see it!
見えた！
Let's go!
行くよ！
Urgent message from the engine room!
運転室より緊急連絡ら
In a moment, the train will get on the railway and accelerate rapidly!
これから線路をつかむと 急速に速度が上がるよ
Hold on tight if you want to keep injuries to a minimum!
軽い傷で済むよう しっかりしがみついてな！
So, we're getting hurt no matter what?
とりあえずケガはするんだ…
Hey!
ええい！
Behave!
言うことを聞きら！
Grandma, that was so, so close!
ばあちゃん！惜しい惜しい！
A little to the right!
もう少し右～！
Just wait and see!
見てらあ！
I'll make it next–
次は決めて…
Huh?!
えっ！？
Chimney! Gonbe!
チムニー！ゴンベ！
You two snuck on board?!
おめえら　ついてきてたのかい？
Yep, we did!
来てたー！
For crying out loud!
何てこったい！
Hurry up and get inside!
早く中へ入んな！
You'll be blown away!
吹き飛んじまうよ！
We're okay! We're okay!
大丈夫大丈夫！
Chimney!
チムニー！
I'm gonna fall!
落ちる～！
D-Don't let go!
て…　手を離すんらないよ！
I'm gonna blow away!
飛ばされる～っ！
H-Hold on a sec, okay?
ちょ…　ちょっと待っちらよ
I'll stop the train right away!
今止めるから
Oh, that's right!
そうら
The brake doesn't work on this train!
こいつブレーキ利かなかったんら
What the heck? That looks kinda fun.
何だ？何か楽しそうだな
It's Straw Hat guy!
麦わらの兄ちゃんだ！
Hi!
おーい！
Straw Hat! Hurry and get Chimney and Gonbe inside!
麦わら！早くチムニーたちを！
Once we get on the railway, they'll be blown away!
このまま線路に乗ったら 吹き飛ばされちまうよ！
Okay!
おう！
– I thought I was a goner.
–　死ぬかと思った
Well, obviously! Good grief!
当たり前らよ　まったく
I told you, didn't I?!
だから言ったらろ
I said you'd get blown away!
吹っ飛ばされるって
Ow, ow, ow...
いたた…
That acceleration sure was crazy.
しっかし ものすげえ加速だな
Honestly...
まったく
Yeah, really, that scared me!
いやいや　ビビった
I hit my lower back.
腰打った…
Wait a minute...
ちょっと待て
We've got some unexpected company.
この車両におかしなヤツらがいるぞ
– What?! Who are they?!
–　何！？そりゃ誰だ！
He means you guys!
お前らだよ！
That includes you!
おめえもだろ！
No matter how hard I tried to stop you, you kept going.
お前らはいくら止めようとしても止まらなかった
The enemy you'd go this far to rescue your friend from
お前らがそうまでして仲間を奪い返したい敵は
is the same one who tried to kill Mr. Iceburg.
俺にとっても アイスバーグさんの命を狙った犯人でもある
And I've got some choice words for them!
それにあいつらには言ってやりたいことがたくさんあるからな
Paulie! We're not gonna let you hog all the glory!
パウリー 抜け駆けは許さんぞ
We figured we'd be able to find Mr. Iceburg's assassins if we followed you,
俺たちはお前にくっついてくりゃ アイスバーグさんの敵に会えると踏んで
so we hid in the coal car!
一緒に炭水車に隠れていたんだ
And... it seems we were right.
案の定　そういうことらしいな
Let us join you guys in this battle.
この戦い 俺たちも加えてもらうぞ
And your enemy is, of course...
その敵ってのは当然
the same bastards who took Big Bro Franky!
フランキーのアニキを連れ去ったヤツらでもある
That's right, and we know exactly who they are!
そうだわいな あたしらそいつが誰なのかもはっきりと知ってるんだわいな
So, Galley-La, how you gonna make it right if we don't get back our Big Bro?!
やいガレーラ！あんたらアニキに何かあったら どう責任取るんだわいな！
Shut up!
黙れ！
It's Mr. Iceburg who's suffered the most!
一番つらいのはアイスバーグさんだ！
What are you guys talking about?!
お前ら何をごちゃごちゃと
Paulie, fill us in! What's going on?!
パウリー！まず俺たちに説明しろ どうなってんだ
He's right, Paulie.
そうだぜパウリー
You know the true culprit, don't you?
知ってんだろ？真犯人を
Just tell us.
お前の口から言ってみな
We're not that dense.
俺たちもそうそう鈍くねえ
We have a rough idea who it is.
おおかたの見当はついてる
We're not gonna be surprised.
別に驚きゃしねえよ
Yeah, it probably became obvious when they suddenly vanished.
まあ　急に意味なく姿を消せば 察しもつくか
Then, I'll tell you straight.
じゃあ　はっきり言う
The true identities of those masked men are...
仮面のヤツらの正体は
Lucci, Kaku, Kalifa and Blueno from the bar.
ルッチ　カク　カリファ そして酒場のブルーノ
They tried to kill Mr. Iceburg.
あいつらが アイスバーグさんを殺そうとした
What?! It wasn't obvious to you?!
想像だにしてなかったのか！
B-But you said they moved back home!
し…　しかし あいつらは里帰りしたって…
At a time like this?!
するか！この非常時に
We thought it was Michael and Hoichael from the Backstreets.
俺たちはてっきり 裏町のマイケルホイケルだと…
Yeah, yeah!
そうそう！
Who and who?!
誰だよそれ
Wh-What?! You don't know them?!
えっ　ええ！？ お前知らねえのか？
They're famous in the Backstreets!
裏町じゃ有名だぞ
Yeah, yeah!
そうだそうだ！
How would I know?! You guys are–
知るか！大体お前らなあ…
Alright!
うっし！
Oh man, I ate a lot.
あ～　食った食った
I'm finally full.
やっと腹いっぱいになったぞ
Well, then...
じゃあまあ…
Franky Family! Galley-La shipwrights!
フランキー一家とも ガレーラの船大工とも
We may have had our issues back in town, but we're all after the same enemy now!
町じゃゴタゴタあったけど この先ここにいる全員の敵は同じだ
That pigeon jerk will be the strongest guy we fight.
これから戦う中で 一番強えのは特にあのハトのヤツだ
He's mine. I'm gonna kick his ass!
あいつは必ず俺がぶっ飛ばす！
Yeah.
そうだな
This is a battle to get back what those four took from us.
この戦いは取られたもんを あの４人から奪い返す戦いだ
In any case, we won't be able to get anything done unless we catch up to them.
ともかく　あいつらに追いつかねえことにゃ 何も終わらねえ
Grandma! Grandma! It's Aqua Laguna!
ばあちゃん　ばあちゃん アクア･ラグナだ！
Oh? It's here already?
おっ　早速来たかい
Chimney, let me have a look!
チムニー　ちょっと見せて
This is bad!
ヤバい！
Miss Kokoro, shouldn't you be in the engine room right now?!
ココロさん こんな時に運転室から離れていいの？
We need to dodge that huge wave somehow!
どうにかして　あの高波を…
Didn't I tell you?
言ったろ
We can't control Rocketman.
ロケットマンは制御不能
Even if we tried to operate it, nothing works, including the brake.
運転しようにも ブレーキも何にも利きゃあしねえんら
My job ended once the train got on the railway.
あたしの仕事は列車を線路にのせるまで
This train always runs at full throttle.
従って 列車は常にフルスロットル
No one can stop it anymore.
もう誰にも止められねえんら！
No way...
ウソ…
Luffy!
ルフィ！
Do something, or we'll crash into that massive wave! Hey, Luffy–
このままじゃ列車が大波に… ねえ　ルフィってば…
If we have the same goal...
せっかく同じ方向向いてるもんが
it would be dumb to fight separately.
バラバラに戦っちゃ意味がねえ
Yeah.
ああ
You're right.
そうだな
Got it? We're comrades.
いいか　俺たちは同志だ
All our friends...
先に出た海列車には
are in that train up ahead.
俺たちの仲間も乗り込んでる
We'll only get more allies!
戦力はまだまだ上がる
You guys!
お前ら！
We're not gonna let a big wave take us down!
大波なんかにやられんな！
We'll all achieve our goal!
全員目的を果たすんだ！
Let's go!
行くぞーっ！
– Yeah!
–　おう！
Now, guys!
さあおめえら！
Show me what you can do about this wave!
この波何とかしてみせな！
Alright! Fire all the cannonballs we have at that wave!
よーし！とにかく ありったけの大砲を波に撃ち込むんだ！
When it comes to cannons, leave it to me!
うお～っ 大砲なら任しとけ！
Franky Family! Stand tall against that wave!
フランキー一家！波にひるむな！
Prepare the cannons!
大砲用意！
– Roger!
–　ラジャー！
Get a move on!
もたもたすんな！
– Yeah!
–　おう！
It's the baby transponder snail!
鳴った　子電伝虫
Hey, you!
おい　お前
Yes, Captain T-Bone!
はっ！Ｔボーン大佐
What happened to your arm?
どうした？その腕の傷
Oh...
ああ
I-I got bitten by a bug earlier. When I scratched the area, it bled.
こ…　これはさっき 虫に刺されてかいたら血が…
That's awful! We must stop the bleeding at once!
いかん！すぐに止血を
Let's make do with this.
これで間に合わせよう
Y-Your own cape?!
そ…　そんな 大切なマントを！
Now, this should do.
これでよい
When my subordinates bleed, it's my heart that gets wounded.
部下が血を流し 傷つくのは私の心だ
Captain T-Bone...
Ｔボーン大佐…
May the world be peaceful and kind again today.
今日も平和で 世界が優しく　ありますように
– His face is super scary.
–　顔がめっちゃ怖い…
Captain!
大佐！
What'd you say?!
何！？
I... I haven't said anything.
ま…　まだ何も言ってませんが…
If it's something I can do, I'll do it, even if my body gets destroyed.
私にできることなら たとえこの身が滅びようとも
Well...
あ…　いえ…
The officials in cars six and seven have been wiped out.
第６第７車両の役人たちが全滅しています
In addition, the two criminals detained in car six are missing as well.
さらに第６車両に勾留中の 罪人２人の消息も不明です
What?!
何だと！？
We can't tell whether there's an intruder or if they escaped on their own.
侵入者がいるのか 罪人たちの自力の脱走か何も分かりません
How can this be?!
何ということだ
Tend to the wounded right away and alert everyone to the situation!
すぐに人命救助！ さらにこの事態を全車両に報告せよ！
Yes, sir!
はっ！
Hey, Nami!
ナミさん
Nami, can you hear me?
ナミさん聞こえるか？
Yes! Is that you, Sanji?!
うん！サンジ君ね
Things are taking a turn for the worse here.
こちらはちょっと まずいことになってきた
Turn for the worse?
まずいこと？
Sanji! Who's with you?!
サンジ君何？今の声
Hey! What's going on?! Sanji!
ねえどうしたの？サンジ君！
Hey, hey...
おいおい
Yeah, thanks to a certain idiot.
ああ　アホのせいで…
I-Idiot?
ア…　アホ？
Oh! Again! What?!
わっ！また！何？
Are you okay?!
大丈夫か？お前
What's going on?!
何が起こってんの？
Are you okay, Sanji? Just kidding.
なんてな ねえ大丈夫？サンジ君！
But you look panicky. Who is this idiot?!
アホって誰？ 一死だぞ　おい
Actually, there are two idiots.
いや　アホ２人だった
Demi-Cannon!
デミキャノン！
– Let 'er rip!
–　食らえ！
We're not even making a dent.
穴も開かねえ
Guess it's no surprise.
当然か…
No! Those puny cannons won't work!
ダメだダメだ！そんなんじゃ！
Guys! Stay back!
みんな下がってろ！
Leave it to the Franky Family's special cannon!
フランキー一家特製大砲に任しとけ！
Target! Aqua Laguna!
目標アクア･ラグナ！
Fire!
撃て！
Super Scrap Cannon!
スーパースクラップ砲！
Dammit!
クッソ…
Stand tall!
ひるむな！
Keep firing!
どんどん撃ち込め！
Replenish the cannonballs!
砲弾の補充を！
Got it!
分かった
Aim at the front! Focus on one spot!
正面を狙え！一点集中だ！
Go! Focus pocus!
いっちゃえ～！ チューチューだあ！
Do your best.
頑張んな
The railway floats a little bit, but not enough to go over Aqua Laguna.
線路は多少浮上するが アクア･ラグナは越えられない
If we slam into it head-on, even Rocketman will be scrap metal.
直撃すりゃ あこのロケットマンもひとったまりもねえや
Are we gonna die?!
俺たち死んじまうのか？
I told you to prepare yourselves, right?
だから言ったろ 覚悟を決めなって
What?! Us too?!
ええっ！？私たちも？
I see...
そう…
Then Robin is still...
ロビンは　まだ…
It sure sounds lively over there.
しっかし そっちはずいぶんにぎやかだな
Say, Sanji...
ねえ　サンジ君
I'll fill you in on Robin's reasoning...
ロビンの行動の訳と…
and our current situation, so...
あたしたちの今の状況を…
Shut the hell up!
うるさーい！
Listen, Sanji.
いい？サンジ君
I'll tell you everything about the reason for Robin's actions and our current situation.
今からロビンの行動の理由と あたしたちの今の状況を全て話すから
So listen closely.
よく聞いて
We're gonna crash!
ぶつかるぞー！
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
ヤベえ　死ぬ！
We're gonna die!
死んじまう
Less whining, more firing!
泣き言言う暇があったら撃て！
Find a way out!
活路を開け！
Hey, Luffy.
おい　ルフィ
Yeah...
ああ…
Let's go, Zoro.
行くぞ　ゾロ
Hey! Keep firing at the front!
おい！正面に撃ち続けろ！
What are you guys doing?!
お前ら何する気だ！
We're gonna fire our own...
大砲を…
cannon.
撃つ
What's 108 times 2?
108を２つでいくつだ？
So, 216...
216って
That's a mouthful.
長いし言いにくいぞそれ
Then, pick whatever.
なら　何でもいいよ
Wh-What are they doing?!
な…　何やってんだ？あいつら
What can they do with their fists and some swords?!
丸腰と刀でどうしようってんだよ
They told us to keep firing.
撃ち続けろって言ってたぞ
Enough talking! Just back them up!
何でもいいから援護しろ！
– Yeah!
–　おう！
Okay, then... 300!
よし！じゃあ300！
Okay!
ああ
Gum-Gum...
ゴムゴムの～
Three-Hundred-Pound...
三百ポンド…
– We're gonna crash!
–　ぶつかる～っ！
– ...Cannon!
–　キャノン！
– W-We got through!
–　ぬ…　抜けた～っ！
– We got through Aqua Laguna!
–　アクア･ラグナを抜けたぞ～っ！
I thought we were gonna die!
死ぬかと思った
Hey! Are you okay, Nami?
おい　ナミさん大丈夫かい？
Yeah, somehow...
ええ　何とか…
That was really something.
こりゃ大したもんら
They don't call themselves pirates for nothing.
だてじゃねえようらね　海賊ども
I'd hate to be their enemy,
敵に回すと恐ろしいが
but they sure make dependable allies!
味方となると これ以上に頼もしいヤツらはいねえな
– Straw Hat!
–　麦わら～！
Honestly, I thought we were dead.
さすがに死を覚悟したぜ
What incredible guys...
なんてヤツらだ
Don't let your guard down.
気ぃ抜くんじゃねえよおめえら
We're not through the storm yet!
嵐はまだ抜けちゃいねえんら
– Yeah!
–　おう！
There's nothing we're afraid of now!
もう怖いもんねえぞ！
That was fun!
面白かったあ！
Straw Hat! You're amazing!
麦わら！すごいわいな
That was some superhuman power!
あんたたち 人間業じゃないわいな
Oh, sorry.
ああ　悪い悪い
Luffy, get over here.
ルフィ！こっち来て
It's Sanji.
サンジ君
Hey, is that you, Luffy?
ようルフィか
Oh, Sanji!
おうサンジ！
How's it going over there?
そっちはどうだ？
Where's Robin?
ロビンは？
Robin is still in their custody.
ロビンちゃんは まだ捕まったままだ
Nami just brought me up to speed.
ナミさんから今事情を聞いたところさ
I heard everything.
全部…　聞いた
I see.
そっか
Yeah...
うん
Well... that's what's going on.
まあ　そういうことだ
Go ahead and give them hell.
いいぞ　暴れても
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
ルフィムチャ言うな！
Tell him to wait until we catch up!
俺たちが追いつくまで 待たせろ！
Hey, cook! Can you hear me?!
おいコック！聞こえるか？
There are some crazy guys over there–
その列車にはヤベえヤツらが…
I said it's fine.
いいって
Zoro...
ゾロ
What would you do if it were you?
お前なら　どうした？
After hearing how Robin lied and was arrested to save us,
ロビンがウソをついてまで 俺たちを救うために捕まったと聞かされて
could you just stay put?
おめえはじっとしてられんのか？
It's no use trying to stop him.
止めたって無駄だ
You know me well.
分かってんなあ
Hey, Moss Head!
おう　マリモ君
Are you worried about me?
俺を心配してくれてんのかい？
Get real, dumbass!
するかバカ！
Unfortunately...
だが残念
after hearing how Robin was feeling...
そんなロビンちゃんの 気持ちを聞かされちゃあ
even if our captain ordered it...
たとえ船長命令でも
there's no way I'd stop!
俺は止まる気はねえんで！
Why'd you break it?!
何で壊しちまうんだよ！
I wanted to ask Straw Hat something, too!
俺も麦わらに 聞きてえことがあったのに！
Huh? Who cares?
あ？知るか
You should've told me beforehand.
前もって言わねえからだ
Even if I didn't tell you, wasn't it obvious?!
言わなくても当然だろうが！
Don't be so arrogant!
すかしてんじゃねえよ！
I'm not being arrogant.
すかしてるよ
I wonder if he'll be okay.
大丈夫かしら…
Lady! Have the train go even faster!
ばあさん 列車もっとスピード出してくれ
Even faster?
もっと？
Yeah! Like, more whooosh!
ああ！もっとビュ～ンと！
Don't worry.
安心しな
It's already exceeded its speed limit...
もう既に船の限界速度を超えてるよ
and it can no longer stop on its own.
もう自力じゃ止まれねえほどにね
So, while I was away...
俺が一味を抜けてる間に
all of this was happening?
そんなことが起きていたのか…
Robin doesn't know about the Merry...
ロビンちゃんはメリー号の件も
or the huge fight between you and Luffy.
ルフィとお前が大ゲンカしたことも 何にも知らねえ
In order for all six of us, including you, to stay safe,
お前を含めた俺たち６人が 全員無事でいられるようにと
she sacrificed herself and obeyed their orders.
ロビンちゃんは自分の身を犠牲にして あいつらの言いなりになって行ったんだ
She did it for us.
俺たちのために
What a moving story!
いい　話じゃねえか…
Why are you crying?
何でお前が泣いてんだ
You dummy! I'm not crying!
バカ！泣いてねえよ
Dammit! I can't believe it!
ちきしょう！何てこったい
Nico Robin is supposed to be a cruel, savage, she-devil!
ニコ･ロビンってのは　世間に言わせりゃ 冷酷非道の悪魔の女のはず
But in reality, she's got a soft spot for her friends!
それがどうだ！ そのほろり仲間慕情！
Robin is within a stone's throw.
ロビンちゃんは目と鼻の先にいる
I'm going to rescue her!
とにかく俺は救出に行くぞ！
Well said!
よし！
I'm the boss of the Franky Family, the Franky!
このフランキー一家棟梁 フランキー
I'll give you a hand, eyebrow bro!
手を貸すぜ 眉毛のお兄ちゃん
To be honest, I've got my own reasons for keeping Robin out of government custody.
訳あって実は俺もロビンが政府に 捕まっちゃあ困る立場にあんのよ
Most of all, when I hear such a touching story...!
何より そんな人情話聞かされちゃあ…
Hey! Let's go, Long Nose!
おい　行くぞ！長っ鼻
I'm...
俺は…
not coming.
いいよ
It no longer has anything to do with me, right?
もう俺には関係ねえじゃねえか
If the World Government itself becomes your enemy at last,
いよいよ世界政府そのものが敵になるんだったら
I don't wanna be part of it.
俺は関わりたくねえし
You'll join with Luffy and the others as well, right?
ルフィたちとも 合流するんだろ？
After all my blustering, and after humiliating myself,
あれだけたんか切って醜態さらして
how could I stand alongside you guys?!
どの面下げて お前らと一緒にいられるってんだよ！
I'm sorry about Robin,
ロビンには悪いが
but I'm no longer under any obligation to go save her!
俺にはもう 助けに行く義理もねえ
I left the Straw Hat Pirates!
俺は一味をやめたんだ！
See ya.
じゃあな
H-Hey! What do you mean "see ya"?!
お…　おい！じゃあなって…
You've got nowhere to go!
おめえ どこにも逃げ場はねえぞ！
It's fine.
いいよ
Leave him be.
ほっとけ
What a stubborn idiot.
意地張りやがって…
Search every nook and cranny!
くまなく捜せー！
There's gotta be some evidence somewhere!
何か証拠が出るはずだ！
This...
こ…
This isn't good!
これはいかん
Please make do with this!
これで間に合わせよう
Wanze, sir! The train is in a whole lot of trouble!
ワンゼさん　列車内　今もう大変で…
Pipe down!
うるせえ！
I'm the one who's in a whole lot of trouble!
もう大変なのはこっちだ！
Nero, sir! The criminals have escaped!
ネロさん！罪人たちが脱走を
I found them!
見つけた！
Oh, crap!
あっ　しまった！
Metallic Star!
メタリック･スター！
– Who's there?!
–　誰だ！
He told me everything.
話は全て彼から聞いたよ
I heard that you men wish to rescue a fair maiden.
お嬢さんを１人助けたいそうだな
That alone is reason enough for me to lend a hand.
そんな君たちに手を貸すのに 理由はいらない
I shall fight alongside you!
私も共に戦おう！
You may call me...
私の名は
Sogeking!
そげキング！